Guide to the Ensko Silver Company Records 1938-1968 MS 200
New-York Historical Society
Ensko Silver Company records
1938-1968
New-York Historical Society
Ensko Silver Company (New York, N.Y.)
MS 200
45 Linear feet in 46 boxes
TBD
Access Restrictions
Open to qualified researchers.
Arrangement
TBD
Biographical / Historical
TBD
Immediate Source of Acquisition
TBD
Related Materials
TBD
Scope and Contents
TBD
- Photos--reproductions part 1 (Box 1)
- Photos--reproductions part 2 (Box 2)
- Photos--antiques part 1 (Box 3)
- Photos--antiques part 2 (Box 4)
- Petty cash, bank statements, 1965-1968 (Box 5)
- Bank statements, check stubs, 1959-1968 (Box 6)
- Letter files A-H, part 1, 1947-1950 (Box 7)
- Letter files A-H, part 2, 1947-1950 (Box 8)
- Letter files I-S, 1947-1950 (Box 9)
- Unlabeled correspondence, 1938-1959 (Box 10)
- Letter files T-Z, bank statements, 1947-1950 (Box 11)
- Letter files, 1966 (Box 12)
- Letter files A-O, 1965 (Box 13)
- Letter files, 1967 (Box 14)
- Letter files, 1968 (Box 15)
- Letter files P-Z, A-F, 1964-1965 (Box 16)
  Scope and Contents
  Letters from 1965, P-Z. Letters from 1964 A-F.
- Letter files G-Z, 1964 (Box 17)
- Letter files part 1, 1963 (Box 18)
- Letter files part 2, 1963 (Box 19)
- Letter files A-L, 1962 (Box 20)
- Letter files M-Y, 1962 (Box 21)
- Letter files A-I, 1961 (Box 22)
- Letter files J-Z, 1961 (Box 23)
- Letter files A-L, 1960 (Box 24)
- Letter files M-Z, 1960 (Box 25)
- Shipping lists, 1961-1967 (Box 26)
- Shipping lists, employment records, deliveries, 1950-1959 (Box 27)
- Receipts, invoices, orders (Box 28)
- Receipts, invoices, orders (Box 29)
- Letter files A-L, 1955 (Box 30)
- Letter files M-Z, A-B, 1955-1956 (Box 31)
  M-Z letters from 1955. A-B letters from 1956.
- Letter files B-L, 1952 (Box 32)
- Letter files M-Z, 1952 (Box 33)
- Correspondence part 1, 1969-1970 (Box 34)
- Correspondence part 2, 1969-1970 (Box 35)
- Insurance policies, invoices, receipts (Box 36)
- Correspondence, orders (Box 37)
- Correspondence, engraving records (Box 38)
- Letter files A-L, 1959 (Box 39)
- Letter files M-Z, 1959 (Box 40)
- Letter files A-F, misc., 1958 (Box 41)
- Letter files G-Z, 1958 (Box 42)
- Letter files A-I, 1957 (Box 43)
- Letter files J-Z, 1957 (Box 44)
- Letter files part 1, 1956 (Box 45)
- Letter files part 2, 1956 (Box 46)